cstrike-planet.com 2010-06-25

# Counter-Strike - Privacy Policy

cstrike-planet.com [referred to herein as CSP] 

### CSP's Privacy

Any personal information you provide to us including and similar to your name, address, telephone number and e-mail address will not be released, sold, or rented to any entities or individuals outside of CSP. 

From time to time, we may use user information for new, unanticipated uses not previously disclosed in our privacy notice. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes to our Web site to notify you of these changes and provide you with the ability to opt out of these new uses. If you are concerned about how your information is used, you should check back at our Web site periodically. Upon request we provide users with access to unique identifier information (e.g., userid, username, or password) that we maintain about them, a description of information that we maintain about them. Upon request we offer users the ability to have inaccuracies corrected and the ability to withdrawal the user account upon request. 

Please note that contributions you make to the site (comment postings, news, uploaded files, and other submitted content writings), under our terms of use, are ours to use; it becomes our property to (delete, republish, or modify) as we like without notice. 

### Cookies

A "cookie" is a small data text file that is placed in your browser which identifies you as a unique user. When you first login, we send your computer a "cookie" to store visitors preferences, alert visitors to new areas that we think might be of interest to them when they return to our site, record past activity in order to provide better service when visitors return to our site, customize Web page content based on visitors' browser type or other information that the visitor sends. 

Most browsers have the ability to accept cookies by default. You may choose to disable cookies via your browser settings, However, some parts of CSP may not function properly if you choose to disable cookies. 

### Ads Serving

To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we have partnered with other companies that we allow to place ads on our webpages. 

CSP is not responsible for the content of external internet sites. You are advised to read the privacy policy of external sites before clicking and or disclosing any personal information. 

Registered users may choose to completely disable advertisements. 

### Security

Remember the risks whenever you use the internet. While we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information that you transmit to CSP and you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any passwords or other account information. In addition other Internet sites or services that may be accessible through CSP have separate data and privacy practices independent of us, and therefore we disclaim any responsibility or liability for their policies or actions. 

Please contact those vendors and others directly if you have any questions about their privacy policies. 

We have appropriate security measures in place in our physical facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site. If you feel that this site is not following its stated information policy, you may contact us at the below addresses or phone number. 

For any other information email: privacy -at- cstrike-planet.com   
Or by telephone: USA 1+ (914) 509-3117 

### Policy Change

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at any time without notice. It is the responsibility of the visitor to visit and periodically check the policy for any changes that might affect their use of CSP. 

_Last updated: September 16th, 2003_
